<resources>
    <string name="app_name">World</string>
    <string name="app_bar_name">30 Best Places In The World</string>
    <string name="world_name_1">1. Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="world_name_2">2. Bali</string>
    <string name="world_name_3">3. Banff</string>
    <string name="world_name_4">4. Barcelona</string>
    <string name="world_name_5">5. Bora Bora</string>
    <string name="world_name_6">6. British Island</string>
    <string name="world_name_7">7. Costa Rica</string>
    <string name="world_name_8">8. Dubai</string>
    <string name="world_name_9">9. Florence</string>
    <string name="world_name_10">10. Glacier National Park</string>
    <string name="world_name_11">11. Grand Canyon</string>
    <string name="world_name_12">12. Great Barrier Reef</string>
    <string name="world_name_13">13. London</string>
    <string name="world_name_14">14. Maldives</string>
    <string name="world_name_15">15. Maui</string>
    <string name="world_name_16">16. New York</string>
    <string name="world_name_17">17. New Zealand</string>
    <string name="world_name_18">18. Paris</string>
    <string name="world_name_19">19. Phuket</string>
    <string name="world_name_20">20. Rio de Janeiro</string>
    <string name="world_name_21">21. Rome</string>
    <string name="world_name_22">22. Santorini</string>
    <string name="world_name_23">23. St. Lucia</string>
    <string name="world_name_24">24. Swiss Alps</string>
    <string name="world_name_25">25. Sydney</string>
    <string name="world_name_26">26. Tahiti</string>
    <string name="world_name_27">27. Tasmania</string>
    <string name="world_name_28">28. Tokyo</string>
    <string name="world_name_29">29. Tulum</string>
    <string name="world_name_30">30. Turks And Caicos</string>
    <string name="world_description_1">Famous museums, tulips, canal-lined streets, "coffee shops" and high-end boutiques await you in Amsterdam. Here, you can spend your days gazing at Vincent van Gogh paintings, relaxing in Vondelpark and shopping in The Nine Streets area.</string>
    <string name="world_description_2">Serene temples and beautiful beaches are the biggest draws to this lush Indonesian paradise. Break up your beach time with a visit to the village of Kintamani, home to a towering (and active) volcano, as well as a large lake. </string>
    <string name="world_description_3">An Alberta town full of acclaimed restaurants, breweries, boutiques and art galleries, Banff makes for an exciting vacation in every season. Vacationers can spend their days hiking, relaxing in hot springs and boating on scenic lakes.</string>
    <string name="world_description_4">This Spanish city is a feast for the eyes: Visitors can walk past medieval architecture in the Barri Gòtic, snap photos of the intricate Basílica de la Sagrada Família and marvel at more of Antoni Gaudís whimsical creations in Park Guell.</string>
    <string name="world_description_5">The islands extinct volcano, Mount Otemanu, makes for a great photo-op or challenging hike, and the friendly Bora Bora locals can help you catch a glimpse of the islands best sights during an off-road excursion.</string>
    <string name="world_description_6">If picturesque beaches and warm weather are what youre after, look no further than the British Virgin Islands. For easy access to Smugglers Cove, Brewers Bay, and other top-notch BVI beaches, consider booking your hotel room on Tortola, the areas largest island.</string>
    <string name="world_description_7">From volcanic mountains and verdant rainforests to tumbling waterfalls and miles of stunning shoreline, Costa Rica is a Central American gem.</string>
    <string name="world_description_8">Stunning Persian Gulf views, heart-pumping activities and historical landmarks await you in Dubai. This Middle Eastern city is filled with some of the worlds most notable and unique attractions, including the Dubai Mall</string>
    <string name="world_description_9">Florence, Italy, offers numerous world-famous attractions, including the Duomo, Piazzale Michelangelo and Piazza della Signoria. </string>
    <string name="world_description_10">Snow-capped peaks, alpine meadows and azure lakes are just a few reasons why Glacier National Park is one of Americas most striking parks.</string>
    <string name="world_description_11">Measuring roughly 277 miles long, 18 miles wide and about a mile deep, the Grand Canyon is brimming with outdoor activities for everyone from day-trippers to adventure junkies.</string>
    <string name="world_description_12">At Australias Great Barrier Reef, youll find more than 600 islands and 1,500-plus species of fish.</string>
    <string name="world_description_13">London is a world unto itself. The eclectic neighborhoods, which are home to a blend of historical landmarks and modern-day attractions, can keep you occupied for days.</string>
    <string name="world_description_14">It is not cheap or easy to reach, but this isolated Indian Ocean vacation spot located southwest of India is the personification of a dreamy tropical retreat.</string>
    <string name="world_description_15">Whether youre driving along the Road to Hana, enjoying a birds-eye view of Mauis lush coastline from a helicopter, snorkeling with sea turtles or simply relaxing on white or black sand beaches</string>
    <string name="world_description_16">New York City hosts infinite urban adventures: You can wander through Central Park, tour art exhibits at The Metropolitan Museum of Art, catch a classic New York Broadway show or peruse SoHos stylish boutiques.</string>
    <string name="world_description_17">New Zealands South Island brims with majestic landscapes at every turn, from dramatic mountains to spectacular fjords.</string>
    <string name="world_description_18">France magnetic City of Light is a perennial tourist destination, drawing visitors with its iconic attractions, like the Eiffel Tower.</string>
    <string name="world_description_19">Located in southern Thailand, the island of Phuket offers something for everyone, especially budget-minded travelers.</string>
    <string name="world_description_20">Christ the Redeemer, Sugarloaf Mountain and the shores of Copacabana and Ipanema beaches are just a few reasons why you should plan a trip to Rio.</string>
    <string name="world_description_21">When you visit Italy capital city, prepare to cross a few must-see landmarks – including the Colosseum, the Trevi Fountain and the Pantheon – off of your bucket list.</string>
    <string name="world_description_22">Frequently touted as a top honeymoon destination, Greeces most popular isle woos newlyweds every year with its breathtaking sunsets, whitewashed villages and colorful beaches.</string>
    <string name="world_description_23">Dotted with luxurious boutique hotels and stunning mountainside resorts, this Caribbean destination is ideal for lovebirds and adrenaline junkies.</string>
    <string name="world_description_24">Snow-covered mountains, charming towns and flower-strewn meadows make the Swiss Alps a year-round fairy tale destination.</string>
    <string name="world_description_25">Sydney offers more than just a dizzying array of famous landmarks, such as the Sydney Opera House, Mrs. Macquaries Chair and the Sydney Harbour Bridge.</string>
    <string name="world_description_26">Travel to this island – the largest in French Polynesia – if you have been dreaming of a vacation spent lazing in a lavish overwater bungalow combined with experiencing an ancient culture.</string>
    <string name="world_description_27">Set your sights on a far-flung adventure down under in Tasmania, Australias island state located about 150 miles from the mainland.</string>
    <string name="world_description_28">Simply setting foot in Japan frenetic capital city is an experience. Known for its bustling streets and flashing neon signs, Tokyo has an electric energy and ample top attractions to discover.</string>
    <string name="world_description_29">Consider Tulum if you are longing for an approachable Bohemian beach getaway. This relatively easy-to-reach Mexico hot spot lies nearly 80 miles southwest of Cancún and boasts many sandy, palm-lined beaches.</string>
    <string name="world_description_30">Located north of the Dominican Republic, this collection of roughly 100 islands and cays is popular with honeymooners – and for good reason. With sparkling white sand, crystal-clear water and nearly 350 miles of colorful coral reef.</string>
    <string name="about">About :-</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about a world.</string>
</resources>